
let questions=[
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Which artist is known for coining the term 'Surrealism'?",
    "options": ["Pablo Picasso", "Salvador Dali", "Vincent van Gogh", "Henri Matisse"],
    "answer": "Salvador Dali",
    "category": "modern-art"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "Which movement is associated with the use of abstract forms and shapes in art?",
    "options": ["Impressionism", "Expressionism", "Futurism", "Cubism"],
    "answer": "Cubism",
    "category": "modern-art"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "Which artist is known for painting the work 'The Persistence of Memory'?",
    "options": ["Pablo Picasso", "Salvador Dali", "Vincent van Gogh", "Henri Matisse"],
    "answer": "Salvador Dali",
    "category": "modern-art"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "Which artist is known for creating the painting 'The Scream'?",
    "options": ["Vincent van Gogh", "Salvador Dali", "Edvard Munch", "Claude Monet"],
    "answer": "Edvard Munch",
    "category": "modern-art"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What movement was associated with the use of bold, bright colors and thick brushstrokes?",
    "options": ["Impressionism", "Expressionism", "Fauvism", "Cubism"],
    "answer": "Fauvism",
    "category": "modern-art"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What movement was associated with the use of bright colors, simplified forms, and a focus on movement and speed",
    "options": ["Impressionism", "Futurism", "Surrealism", "Abstract Expressionism"],
    "answer": "Futurism",
    "category": "modern-art"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Water Lilies'?",
    "options": ["Claude Monet", "Paul Cezanne", "Paul Gauguin", "Paul Klee"],
    "answer": "Claude Monet",
    "category": "modern-art"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Les Demoiselles d'Avignon'?",
    "options": ["Henri Matisse", "Vincent van Gogh", "Salvador Dali", "Pablo Picasso"],
    "answer": "Pablo Picasso",
    "category": "modern-art"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Guernica'?",
    "options": ["Claude Mone", "Paul Cezanne", "Pablo Picasso", "Vincent van Gogh"],
    "answer": "Pablo Picasso",
    "category": "modern-art"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "Which artist is known for creating the sculpture 'The Thinker'?",
    "options": ["Auguste Rodin", "Alexander Calder", "Jean Arp", "Henry Moore"],
    "answer": "Auguste Rodin",
    "category": "modern-art"
  }
]